ctuit.com 2017-12-30

# Privacy Statement | Ctuit

Ctuit Inc. d/b/a Ctuit Software is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you a powerful and user-friendly online experience. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected on our websites that link to this Privacy Policy (the “Websites”) which include but are not limited to [www.ctuit.com](http://www.ctuit.com/), <https://radar.ctuit.com/CtuitNet/login.aspx>, any mobile applications associated with the Websites (the “Mobile Applications”) and all other online offerings that post a link to this Privacy Policy, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology or any associated content, material, or functionality contained on the Websites or Mobile Applications (the “Services” and, together with the Websites and the Mobile Applications, collectively, the “System”).

We encourage you to become familiar with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By accessing and using the System, or any part thereof, you agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy, and that, in exchange for access to the System, you accept and consent to the privacy practices (and any uses and disclosures of information about you) that are described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is a part of the Terms of Use for the System located [here](http://ctuit.com/terms-of-use/) (the “Terms of Use”).

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Ctuit Software collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Ctuit Software also collects demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Ctuit Software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by Ctuit Software for the operation of the System, to maintain quality of the System, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the System.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personal information or personally sensitive data through Ctuit Software public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Ctuit Software encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Ctuit Software so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Ctuit Software is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the System.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Ctuit Software collects and uses your personal information to operate the System and deliver the services you have requested. Ctuit Software also uses your personal information to inform you of other products or services available from Ctuit Software and its affiliates. Ctuit Software may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Ctuit Software does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Ctuit Software may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.

Ctuit Software keeps track of the Websites and pages our customers visit within the System, in order to determine what Ctuit Software services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within the System to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

**Sharing of your Personal Information**

In addition to the uses mentioned or described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy or in the Terms of Use, we may catalog and add your personal information to our database. We may also share your information with any of our affiliates, subsidiaries, or our parent company for the purpose of providing the System, for any other purpose described in this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, or for any other lawful purposes.

Ctuit Software may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Ctuit Software, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Ctuit Software does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, Ctuit Software will not use, disclose, or transfer your personal information unless (1) you expressly authorize Ctuit Software to do so; (2) it is necessary to allow Ctuit Software’s service providers, agents, or other third parties to provide products or services for or to Ctuit Software, (3) it is necessary in order to provide the System or our services, (4) Ctuit Software is sending you other information that may be useful to you, (5) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on Ctuit Software’s behalf or to other entities with whom Ctuit Software has joint marketing agreements, (6) it is necessary to protect the confidentiality or security of your records, (7) it is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, verifying identity, age, and/or payment details, investigating complaints about the System, risk assessment, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, marketing, customer purchasing preferences and trends and dispute resolution, (8) it is necessary to comply with law enforcement, governmental mandate, or other legal requirement, if appropriate, for your protection or in connection with an investigation or prosecution of possible unlawful activity; (9) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Ctuit Software or the merger of Ctuit Software into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which Ctuit Software is not the survivor, or (10) it is otherwise necessary for Ctuit Software to disclose it as required or permitted by law.

**Use of Cookies**

The System uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Ctuit Software pages, or register with the Website or Ctuit Software services, a cookie helps Ctuit Software to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Ctuit Software features that you customized.

We also utilize Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, in order to better understand your use of our System. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visits the System, what pages they visit and what other websites they used prior to visiting. Google uses the data collected to track and examine the use of the System, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on the System to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the System is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Google offers an opt-out mechanism for the web available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Ctuit Software services or the Websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. We take commercially reasonable measures to protect information transmitted via or stored on the System. However, we cannot guarantee that information that users of the System may transmit or otherwise supply will be totally secure. You agree to immediately notify us of any breach of System's security, this Privacy Policy, or the Terms and Conditions of Use of which you become aware.

**California Privacy Rights**

Under California law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (a) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, email, and mailing address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and (b) the name and address of all such third parties. To request the above information, please email us at: [privacy@ctuit.com](mailto:privacy@ctuit.com) with a reference to California Disclosure Information.

**California and Delaware “Do Not Track” Disclosures**

California and Delaware law requires Ctuit Software to indicate whether it honors “Do Not Track” settings in your browser concerning targeted advertising. “Do Not Track” is a standard that is currently under development. As it is not yet finalized, Ctuit Software adheres to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy and does not monitor or follow any Do Not Track browser requests.

**Changes** **to this Privacy Policy**

Ctuit Software will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. All updates and amendments are effective immediately upon notice to you, which we may give by any means, including, but not limited to, by posting a revised version of this Privacy Policy or other notice on the System. Ctuit Software encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how Ctuit Software is protecting your information.

**Visiting The System From Outside The United States**

If you are visiting the System, or any part thereof, from outside of the United States of America, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. By using any portion of the System, you understand and consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Contact Information**

Ctuit Software welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Ctuit Software has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact Ctuit Software at [privacy@ctuit.com](mailto:privacy@ctuit.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

**Acknowledgement**

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SYSTEM, OR ANY PORTION THEREOF, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND CONSENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY, AND TO THE USES AND DISCLOSURES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU, THAT ARE DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE REFERENCED ABOVE.

Last Updated: December 15, 2016
